{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898858693","data":{"timestamp":" 946898858693"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-0-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898864743","data":{"timestamp":" 946898864743"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_5-6-2"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898871871","data":{"timestamp":" 946898871871"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_9-4-0"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898878326","data":{"timestamp":" 946898878325"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-7-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898883335","data":{"timestamp":" 946898883335"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_4-7-5"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898889337","data":{"timestamp":" 946898889337"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898894731","data":{"timestamp":" 946898894731"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_7-2-3"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898901178","data":{"timestamp":" 946898901178"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-5-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898906675","data":{"timestamp":" 946898906675"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-5-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898911395","data":{"timestamp":" 946898911395"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-5-7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898916562","data":{"timestamp":" 946898916562"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_2-3-9"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898924520","data":{"timestamp":" 946898924520"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_5-0-9"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898931138","data":{"timestamp":" 946898931138"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_4-8-9"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898937646","data":{"timestamp":" 946898937646"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-5-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.num:0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898944152","data":{"timestamp":" 946898944152"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 12f6701f-040a-406d-8af3-f5fc125c0dc5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.num_0..9.by.1.rand.s2q.AV.rise.36"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-5-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946898993072","data":{"timestamp":" 946898993071"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kwake_tofauti-kwake-sawa-hii"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kwake"," userResponse":" kwake"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899030468","data":{"timestamp":" 946899030468"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjinga_sawasawa-mjinga-jiwe-rinda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mjinga"," userResponse":" sawasawa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899033189","data":{"timestamp":" 946899033189"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjinga_sawasawa-mjinga-jiwe-rinda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mjinga"," userResponse":" rinda"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899035859","data":{"timestamp":" 946899035859"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjinga_sawasawa-mjinga-jiwe-rinda"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mjinga"," userResponse":" mjinga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899095364","data":{"timestamp":" 946899095364"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kima_mahindi-wanaume-Kima-hebu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Kima"," userResponse":" Kima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_37","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899118542","data":{"timestamp":" 946899118542"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Kima_mahindi-wanaume-Kima-hebu"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899118619","data":{"timestamp":" 946899118619"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 2981545f-b54a-4de2-8d40-28a0278fad75"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_37"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni yeye aliyenialika."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYENIALIKA"," userResponse":" ALIYENIALIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899127137","data":{"timestamp":" 946899127136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899129297","data":{"timestamp":" 946899129297"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899131480","data":{"timestamp":" 946899131480"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899134725","data":{"timestamp":" 946899134724"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899136994","data":{"timestamp":" 946899136994"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899139261","data":{"timestamp":" 946899139260"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899142157","data":{"timestamp":" 946899142157"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899144311","data":{"timestamp":" 946899144311"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899146495","data":{"timestamp":" 946899146494"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899149742","data":{"timestamp":" 946899149741"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899151857","data":{"timestamp":" 946899151856"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899153971","data":{"timestamp":" 946899153970"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899156907","data":{"timestamp":" 946899156906"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899159130","data":{"timestamp":" 946899159129"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899161372","data":{"timestamp":" 946899161371"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899164429","data":{"timestamp":" 946899164429"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899166792","data":{"timestamp":" 946899166791"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899169137","data":{"timestamp":" 946899169136"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899172165","data":{"timestamp":" 946899172164"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899174302","data":{"timestamp":" 946899174302"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899176457","data":{"timestamp":" 946899176457"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899179560","data":{"timestamp":" 946899179560"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899181750","data":{"timestamp":" 946899181749"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899183947","data":{"timestamp":" 946899183946"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899187132","data":{"timestamp":" 946899187132"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899189575","data":{"timestamp":" 946899189574"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899191996","data":{"timestamp":" 946899191996"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899195093","data":{"timestamp":" 946899195092"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899197363","data":{"timestamp":" 946899197363"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899199613","data":{"timestamp":" 946899199613"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899202522","data":{"timestamp":" 946899202522"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899204724","data":{"timestamp":" 946899204723"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899206927","data":{"timestamp":" 946899206926"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899209906","data":{"timestamp":" 946899209905"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899212274","data":{"timestamp":" 946899212273"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899214046","data":{"timestamp":" 946899214046"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946899214096","data":{"timestamp":" 946899214096"," userId":" 6116000839"," sessionId":" 6116000839_20000103_142721"," gameId":" 0022e36c-b0fc-4d3d-9fee-6c699883c12b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_44"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}